Publishing and production companies
are the same, so the series is a-okay.
10 cm distance matters!
Didn't you know?
Haven't seen a new meme for a while...
But, so much fatter now.
I wouldn't have cared in my younger years.
I thought people might be tired of it already,
but it's so damn cute so I took it out again...
I personally like Kinryuu much more,
but for the memes' sake...
That reminds me,
haven't seen Van Damme
for a while now.
U~I~HA~
RU~!
Are you wearing your panties?
Sa-Saten-san!  I...  I am!
Really?
I am!
I am...?
More Complete Railgun
Thanks for waiting.
Here you go.  The last one.
Ew...  I don't want that...
U-Um...  Do you want it?
R-really?!
What, sis?
The smell of death looms, loo loo loo.
The wind roars.
Her presence wasn't detectable at all.
Indeed...
I heard some interesting rumors about the dorm manager a while ago.
I looked up postings on the Internet!
That dorm manager is actually...
Manga "B.B" reference.
Runba!
Judgment!
Knight!
Jalapeño.
She had such a past, apparently.
What?!
T-that sounds so fake...  E-even for her...
Yeah!  Of course it can't be true.
It is true!  A friend of an acquaintance said so!
Yeah!  It's on the Internet so it must be true!
"Sleeping  Sheep"
And it's about a "Sleeping something".
Right?
Burning Blood
And that American soldier name "Burning something".
Yeah, yeah.  "Excessive self-defense", right?
Right?
Is this...  For real...?
I'm s-s-scared...
I wanna eat a shibazuke.
So to sum it up.
In Academy City's current curriculum for power development,
The most important concept is "personal reality".
To put it simply...
Here.
A box with a cat alive in it.
However!
When the cover opens, what would have happened to the cat?
Do you know, Saten?
A-ah!
It could be dead or not dead.
Let's find out!
SF Revival!
Cheers!
A cup after work is just so damn awesome!
Let's start BBQing!
Meat!
No meat for the Anti-Skill that does nothing but cause trouble!
No way!
Don't worry.  You can still get meat even if all you do is cause trouble.
For you see, today we have ourselves the prestigious BBQ set!
Komoe-sensei...
Time to toss them on and stuff them down!
Yomikawa-sensei, can you pass me the sauce please?
Sauce!
Can't eat BBQ without the sauce!
Agreed!
You like "jan" a lot, huh?
And not just these.
For action stars, there's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
For boy inventors, there's Jean.
For mahjong, there's jankyu.
For a crude fate, there's Jean Valjean.
My favorite stuff's got "jan" all over!
And there're more!
For paintings, there's Jean Cocteau.
For cooking, there's Akiyama Jan.
Manga's got Jump.
For teatime, there's Jean-Paul Hévin!
Windmills, Holland, who dat?
Among those marching on Kabukicho,
There's a Hollander in a skirt!!
Hey Kuroko...
What now, sis?
Doesn't Academy City have a whole lot of wind turbines?
I guess.
Are those wind turbines... really making electricity?
Even Holland doesn't have that many wind turbines!
Geez, what makes you say that?
I've heard about this.
All the randomly built wind turbines in Japan are gonna be taken down.
But these turbines are spinning fine though.
They're wind turbines!  Wind turbines!
This is Academy City!  Academy City!
How can they be enough?!  And with what wind?  We're inland!
Spinning fine?!  You think it's mountain wind?  You serious?!
That's total rubbish!
So this is what I think.
Maybe these turbines are spinning using electricity and not making any!
Say what now?!
Sis, please don't be silly.
I'm deadly serious!  Something's not right here.
This city is definitely hiding something!
A conspiracy?  Government secrets?!
Those turbines are a part of the government's secret plan!
And if my deduction is correct!
It's the first step of the Mars migration project: Exodus.
I saw it on an online post.
I heard rumors too!
How...  How could this be...
But only those chosen can escape...
I'm only a level 0 so...
Saten-san, it's nothing like that.
But can mankind alone carry out such a plan?
Extraterrestrials!
Greys are definitely involved!
Ah!  The color grey, huh?!
Stupid, stupid!  Not the color!  Stupid, stupid!
The color grey, huh?
Stupid, stupid!
My dear sis, please calm down.
This is Academy City after all.
I wouldn't be surprised no matter what happens here.
Oh yeah, of course!  This is Academy City after all!
Yeah!
Yes!  Yes!  Sauce!
This is Academy City.
A city occupied by 2.3 million students.
Nothing that happens here is a surprise.
To be continued
Dear my friend
Every day & night
Always be with you
Dear my friend
Every day & night
Always be with you
Please conserve electricity, 'kay?  Biri~biri~
Please conserve electricity, 'kay?  Buri~buri~❤
Please conserve electricity, 'kay?!  DONG!  DONG!
Please conserve electricity, 'kay?  *sniff sniff*
Reduce CO2 emission:  Breathe less.
Sub Smith-2010.02.03